sportsunlimitedinc.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Sports Unlimited, Inc.

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.

#### Sports Unlimited Privacy Policy

#### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

**Sports Unlimited takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.

**How Sports Unlimited Uses Your Personal Information**

This policy covers how Sports Unlimited treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of Sports Unlimited products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**This privacy policy only applies to Sports Unlimited**

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Sports Unlimited does not own or control or to people that Sports Unlimited does not employ or manage

**Sports Unlimited through Yahoo’s participation in the Safe Harbor program**

Yahoo! participates in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. To view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's [Safe Harbor Web site](http://export.gov/safeharbor/). For more information about Yahoo!’s participation in the Safe Harbor program, please visit Yahoo!’s [Safe Harbor](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/safeharbor/) details page.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

**General**

Sports Unlimited collects personal information when you register a “my account”, place an order or enter a promotion. 

When you register an account or place an order with us, we ask for information such as your name, email address, ZIP code and personal interests. Sports Unlimited also collects information about your orders you place at [www.sportsunlimited.com](http://www.sportsunlimited.com/). 

Sports Unlimited automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Sports Unlimited cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. 

Sports Unlimited uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

#### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

Sports Unlimited does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Sports Unlimited under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Sports Unlimited communicate with you about offers from Sports Unlimited and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Sports Unlimited's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  * We transfer information about you if Sports Unlimited is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Sports Unlimited will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### COOKIES

Sports Unlimited may set and use cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Access your information when you "sign in" so we can provide you with customized content or remember the last page you visited on SportsUnlimtied.com.

    * Information that Sports Unlimited collects related to your activities and interests is maintained by Yahoo!

  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are visiting [www.SportsUnlimited.com](http://www.sportsunlimited.com/).

    * When you log in to your Sports Unlimited my account, a cookie that contains information about your interests is placed on the computer or device you are using. This allows Sports Unlimited to associate your interests and activity if you log in to your MyAccount account on multiple devices. This means that your browsing habits on your work computer or a library computer, when logged in, can inform your experience on Sports Unlimited when using your home computer when logged in.

  * Provide general internal and customer analytics.

#### Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

**General**

You can edit your Sports Unlimited My Account Information at any time.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Sports Unlimited service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Sports Unlimited Newsletter, that are considered part of your Sports Unlimited account, unless your account is set to opt out of these communications.

You can delete your Sports Unlimited account by visiting our [My Account](http://myaccount.sportsunlimitedinc.com/) page. 

#### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

Yahoo!’s shopping cart as well as Sports Unlimited’s organization has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read Security at Sports Unlimited through Yahoo!.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Sports Unlimited may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Sports Unlimited account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
